<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on Fergus Taylor</title>
    <link>/categories/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on Fergus Taylor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chamonix and the Conville Course</title>
      <link>/writing/chamonix-and-the-conville-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/chamonix-and-the-conville-course/</guid>
      <description>strong, b { font-weight: 800; } .image { border-radius: unset; } @media screen and (max-width: 480px) { .image.left, .image.right { display: block; width: 100%; max-width: unset; } }  I set off to the Alps for the Conville Mountaineering Course, and learned a few new skills to keep myself safe in the Mountains this year.
*Another group out on Mont Blanc Massif
Back to the Friday before, where I&amp;rsquo;m desperately trying to sort out my equipment before an early-morning flight to Geneva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;You alright?&#39;</title>
      <link>/writing/2016-11-27-you-alright/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/2016-11-27-you-alright/</guid>
      <description>Back in my third year of University I was asked to get involved with the Student Union as an opportunity to improve welfare at the Medical School, in particular - Mental Health.
I had some successes, including the introduction of a new peer support programme. But the issue of advertising the available services so that students were aware of their options when they needed them - has been poorly approached for some time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glasgow ARM - Supporting Rwandan Healthcare Students</title>
      <link>/writing/2016-07-01-glasgow-arm-supporting-rwandan-healthcare-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/2016-07-01-glasgow-arm-supporting-rwandan-healthcare-students/</guid>
      <description>Last year produced several milestones in the development of Glasgow ARM, and with financial charitable recognition came a huge push forward to increase donations.
In order to both thank the Undergraduate Medical School, and highlight the opportunities for further engagement, I wrote the following piece for the 2016 Summer Newsletter.
The article in context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Call for Trustees</title>
      <link>/writing/2016-04-26-a-call-for-trustees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/2016-04-26-a-call-for-trustees/</guid>
      <description>Since my second year at medical school I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in the formation and running of a charity. Having been preparing to step down in my role as Chair, it fell to me to reach out to new potential trustees within the University-wide newsletter.
The writing in context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;We&#39;re going on a bear hunt..&#39;</title>
      <link>/writing/2016-03-08-were-going-on-a-bear-hunt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/2016-03-08-were-going-on-a-bear-hunt-2/</guid>
      <description>This was a piece commissioned by the Glasgow Guardian, regarding current negotiations around the second Junior Doctors’ strike. It followed two opinion pieces by other writers earlier that week; putting their arguments both for and against industrial action.
As a student representative (GUSRC), and medical student, I was invited to “consider [writing on the issue] in order to balance this important debate.”
Given the breadth of coverage I felt this had recieved from the previous writers, as well as elsewhere – I pitched a slightly lesser-covered piece of news from earlier that week, that (with the permission of Michael Rosen), I felt helped frame the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accident Incident Report: 18/06/14</title>
      <link>/writing/2014-06-18-accident-incident-report-180614/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/2014-06-18-accident-incident-report-180614/</guid>
      <description>Previously made for the Glasgow University Canoe Club - the following satarical short piece was written for the Club journal, as a summary of a Summer trip we spent kayaking around Scotland. Unfortunately, mostly using in-jokes to its members.
Details of incident: After a sunny day kayaking on the Garry - sleepy from an afternoon of BBQ and booty beverages - the kayaking group formally known as GUCC, swam, ferry-glided, or were towed across the river to inspect the rocks beside the final drop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Survival: A Doctor Explores the Limits of Human Endurance</title>
      <link>/writing/2012-03-01-extreme-survival-a-doctor-explores-the-limits-of-human-endurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/2012-03-01-extreme-survival-a-doctor-explores-the-limits-of-human-endurance/</guid>
      <description>By Dr Kenneth Kamler
Recounting his experiences with AMS, surviving adrift at sea, as well as performing hand surgery in the not entirely aseptic depths of the Amazonian Rainforest. Dr Kenneth Kamler tells stories of his adventures and those of his friends, to create a gripping depiction of some of the most inhospitable environments in the world and the conditions that can occur in them.
He details his reactions to the injuries and uses his skills as a storyteller to examine the actions doctors take in order to treat under pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>